export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt: "What is React?",
    options: ["language", "framework", "library", "webserver"],
    answer: "library",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of this is not a programming language?",
    options: ["Python", "JavaScript", "MC-03", "Java"],
    answer: "MC-03",
  },

  {
    prompt: "Which of this is not a javascript framework?",
    options: ["React", "angular", "vue", "java"],
    answer: "java",
  },

  {
    prompt: "What is hbs?",
    options: ["language", "framework", "library", "viewengine"],
    answer: "viewengine",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is RegEx?",
    options: [
      "String",
      "JavaScript framework",
      "Sequence of characters",
      "Java viewengine",
    ],
    answer: "Sequence of characters",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What does the Acronym REST Stand for??",
    options: [
      "Representational State Transform",
      "Representational State Transfer",
      " Represent State Transform",
      " Represent State Transfer",
    ],
    answer: "Representational State Transfer",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is the protocol used in REST?",
    options: ["FTP", "SMTP", "HTTP", "JMX"],
    answer: "HTTP",
  },
  {
    prompt: " What is the HTTP Status Code Related to Page Not Found?",
    options: ["303", "404", "500", "401"],
    answer: "404",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Which HTTP method do we use to make an HTTP request to update an existing resource?",
    options: ["PUT", "POST", "UPDATE", "DELETE"],
    answer: "PUT",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which is not REST Architectural Constraints?",
    options: [
      "Client-Server",
      " Stateless",
      " Cacheable",
      "Service orchestration",
    ],
    answer: "Service orchestration",
  },
];
